Ing. David Janča

Born: 1992 **City:** Brno

Phone: +420 721 294 257 **Email:** xjancad@gmail.com



Profile:

I decided to change my career after working for several years in sales. I was always used to work with computers, but just a few months ago I discovered, that I understand programming and I like it. I believe, that I can use my analytical and logical thinking in IT better, than in sales. So for now, I am a beginning programmer. I am working on myself and I am guided by an experienced mentor. Last month I created a logical game app with AI and multiplayer. I am now working on an app for personal finance management. If you want to learn more, you can visit my website: davidj.online

Education:

2011 – 2017	VUT Brno (master's degree) Faculty of chemistry, Chemistry for Medical Applications
03/2015 - 06/2015	Studying abroad in Denmark, Rønshoved Højskole
2022	Harvard CS50's Introduction to Computer Science
2023	Harvard CS50's Web Programming with Python and JavaScript

Work experience:

08/2018 - 09/2019	Sales representative for chromatography consumables
	Company: Pragolab s.r.o.
	Job description: Acquisition of new customers, customer service and
	education, processing quotes and tenders, presentation of the
	company at exhibitions, translations of professional text and articles
09/2019 - 11/2022	Technical and sales representative for powder coatings
	Company: JOTUN CZECH a.s.
	Job description: Acquisition of new customers, customer service and
	education, processing quotes and tenders, handling complaints

Other knowledge and skills:

Languages: English: Advanced

German: Beginner

Compurer knowledge (beginner): Languages: C, Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Frameworks: Express, Django, Flask, React

Other: GIT, Linux, Bash, Node, SQL

Driving licence B – active driver

Course of an etiquette with Ladislav Špaček and End of procrastination with Peter Ludwig and dozens of seminars on personal development, development of business and management skills